Transformation Cookies
Brought to you by: Ko-Fi.me/OrangeFlash
Nobita!
Go buy some snacks to treat our guest!
How troublesome!
Idea! Doraemon, it's shopping time!
Doraemon!
Huh, is he out?
What's this?
Animal Cookies!
Just the right thing!
OK!
Excuse me!
Thanks for waiting!
Why did you have to buy cookies?
It's OK, I love cookies.
Nobita, go buy some decent snacks!
Okay!
This and this, and that as well!
Here is the change.
One... Two... Three... Four...!
Correct!
Why are you staring at my face, mister?
Kitty!
What happened to my face?
Doraemon, help me!
What? You ate that cookie?
But that's Animal Transformation Cookie!
You can't just eat it!
What am I supposed to do now? Meow!
It's effects wear off after a while.
You will lose the cat face, 5 minutes from now.
Oh, really?
See? Told you!
You are right!
You gave the cookies to our guest? You're inviting trouble!
I wonder if he ate it?
Did you eat the cookies, mister?
Do you feel anything strange inside your body?
Are you OK?
One, two, three....!
You had four?
What are you talking about?
How rude of you towards our guest!
What do we do now?
Doraemon, is there any way to prevent the cookies' effects?
Nope, sadly.
Oh my god!
He must have ate the Horse-shaped cookie!
OK!
MIster, please come over here!
I have something very important to tell you!
It's the bathroom!
Thanks!
Nobita, where did you put the cookies that you bought?
I left them at the lobby.
Thank goodness!
Wonder if it's your cup of tea?
Well, the the snack is very tasty!
This time it's chicken.
Mister, go to the bathroom again!
Cut it out!
Gotta do something!
Mister, there's a phone call for you!
But...!
It will ring now!
Who might you be?
Hello, hello! But I'm just a nobody!
What do you want?
Let's chat, just for 1 hour!
What? I have no idea what you are talking about!
Don't know who played this prank on me, I am puzzled!
Wait, it's not changing back yet!
I see.
No, don't look, Mom, don't!
don't
Nobita, what the hell are you doing in front of our guest?
I won't let you go!
Seriously, wonder where they went?
i will take my leave now.
Sorry, I was unable to treat you to any decent snacks!
Mister!
Mister, please stay for a while!
There's one more cookie's effects that must be wore off.
No, I am leaving!
It's a frog face!
Mom must be angry at us!
Right!
I am so shivering, I can't move!
It's Dad!
I am home!
Did you two did something, again?
Don't worry, I will apologize to your mom on the behalf of you two.
I am home!
Welcome home, dear!
Oh no! Mom ate one too!